corbettmaths.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Corbettmaths

## Privacy Policy

At Corbettmaths we make every effort to ensure we protect your personal information.

This site, www.corbettmaths.com (the “Website”) is owned and operated by Corbettmaths. In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), the terms “Corbettmaths”, “we”, “us” and “our” mean Corbettmaths.

This Policy, in conjunction with our [Terms and Conditions](https://corbettmaths.com/2018/05/17/terms-and-conditions/), explains how Corbettmaths may use the information we collect about you, as well as the rights you have over any personal information we hold about you.

Please read this Policy and our [Terms and Conditions](https://corbettmaths.com/2018/05/17/terms-and-conditions/) carefully; by accessing the Website you confirm to have understood and agreed to them.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at corbettmaths@gmail.com

## **Information we collect**

We collect information about you when you:

  * visit the Website – (geographic location, i.e. country, pages visited, referral source)
  * buy revision cards – (name, address and email address)
  * take part in our competitions, surveys and questionnaires – (name, email address – if provided)
  * contact us via e-mail – (name and email address – if provided)

## **How we use your information**

We collect your personal information to help Corbettmaths better understand you and to enable us to personalise your experience with Corbettmaths. We use your information to:

  * administer the website;
  * improve your browsing experience;
  * to contact you regarding orders or queries you have made (non-marketing)
  * process your purchases;
  * develop and improve our website;
  * to keep the website secure;
  * manage competitions, surveys and questionnaires;

## **COOKIES**

### **What is a cookie?**

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your personal computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website. This information is then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user’s device.

You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

### **Cookies used on the Website**

A list of all the cookies used on the Website by category is set out below.

### Visitor cookies

Cookie Name | Duration | Purpose  
---|---|---  
comment_author_{HASH} | 347 days | Remembers the value entered into the [comment form](https://jetpack.com/support/comments/)‘s  **name**  field. Specific to the site from which it is set.  _This cookie mirrors one set by the core WordPress software  [for commenting purposes](https://codex.wordpress.org/WordPress_Cookies)_.  
comment_author_email_{HASH} | 347 days | Remembers the value entered into the [comment form](https://jetpack.com/support/comments/)‘s  **email**  field. Specific to the site from which it is set.  _This cookie mirrors one set by the core WordPress software  [for commenting purposes](https://codex.wordpress.org/WordPress_Cookies)_.  
comment_author_url_{HASH} | 347 days | Remembers the value entered into the [comment form](https://jetpack.com/support/comments/)‘s  **URL**  field. Specific to the site from which it is set.  _This cookie mirrors one set by the core WordPress software  [for commenting purposes](https://codex.wordpress.org/WordPress_Cookies)_  
  
#### **Mobile Theme**

Cookie Name | Duration | Purpose  
---|---|---  
akm_mobile | 3.5 days | Remembers whether or not a user wishes to view the [mobile version](https://jetpack.com/support/mobile-theme/) of a site.  
  
## **Using browser settings to manage cookies**

You are able to use the settings within your browser to control the cookies that can be placed onto your computer.  The ‘Help’ menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether.

## **Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on the third party order forms, PayPal encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). PayPal privacy policy can be found here: <https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

## **Disclosing your information**

We will never disclose your information to anyone outside the Corbettmaths except where we have your consent; where we are required or permitted to do so by law, such as when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process; where other companies who provide a service to us as part of our order process require that data i.e. delivery companies, payment providers.

We do not use your information for any marketing purposes

## **Other websites**

The Website may contain links to other sites which are outside our control and not covered by this Policy. The operators of these sites may collect information from you that will be used by them in accordance with their policy, which may differ from ours.

## **Your rights**

You have a right of access, rectification, restriction, opposition, and erasure.   Please contact us if you wish to exercise these rights.  If you wish to complete an access request to all personal data that Corbettmaths holds on you (which will be your name, address and email address if an order is placed), please note that photo identity will be required to prove your identity.

We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and fulfil our agreements.

## **GPDR**

## **Changes to our policy**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

Page created: 17th May 2018

Last update: 13th June 2018

## **Contacting us**

If you have any queries, please contact us at [corbettmaths@gmail.com](mailto:corbettmaths@gmail.com)
